reflexcash.com 2019-04-17

# Reflex Affiliates | Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

The following statement outlines the privacy policy of . This policy is based on our fundamental goal to provide our business partners with quality information and resources while maintaining individual anonymity and personal privacy. Please forward any comments you may have regarding this policy to . 

### 1\. General Provision

This privacy Policy describes the ways in which your personal data is collected and used by  (having its registered office at 71-75 Shelton Street, Coven Garden, London WC2H 9JQ) acting as the Controller. 

It is your responsibility to review and understand this Privacy Policy prior to providing your personal data to us. If you do not accept and agree to the Privacy Policy, please refrain from providing your personal data to us, accessing our websites, and/or utilizing our products and services. 

With our websites and services constantly evolving, our Privacy Policy may also change from time to time. Whenever there are changes, the modified policies will be posted on our websites and will be effective at that time. Consequently, each time you access or use our websites or otherwise engage with us, you accept and agree to the most current Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to be aware of any such changes. 

### 2\. Data Collected

We may collect personal information from our advertisers and affiliates (hereinafter "You") which are likely to identify you (Personal data) when You (i) register on our platform accessible on the link(hereinafter “Site”), (ii) fill out forms or fields on the Site (iii) sign a contract with us (for example an insertion order) (iv) complete an application for a product or service available through the site and (v) communicate with us by email, mail, text, telephone, facsimile or other electronic means. 

The data collected contains, but is not limited to, in particular the following information: 

  * Company name (if You are a legal person)
  * Name and last name (if You are a natural person)
  * Registration number
  * Passport copy
  * Address
  * Phone, e-mail address and website
  * IP address
  * Name, last name, email address and skype account
  * A copy of the communications between You and Us
  * Details of the financial or accounting transactions carried out by any means containing your bank details. 

### 3\. Purpose of the processing and the lawful basis for the processing

In this context, the processing is necessary for the execution of the contracts concluded between You and  and provide You with the requested information and services, but also the purposes of the processing are: 

  * Send you information about our services by any means of communication
  * Administering inquiries
  * Statistical purposes to see how users use the website and to analyze search behavior, as well as to display content customized for you 
  * Collect your payments or issue payments
  * Allow you to customize your profile on our platform
  * To ensure compliance with (i) the applicable law, (ii) our general conditions of use, (iii) our privacy policy, in case of breaches from You our contractual relations may be suspended 
  * To inform you of changes to our services
  * Accounting, Tax and Budget Management
  * Management of advertisers and affiliates

### 4\. Disclosure of the Data

We reserve the right to disclose and/or transfer Information to another entity if we are acquired by or merged with another company, if we sell or transfer a business unit or assets to another company, as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, or as part of any other similar business transfer. 

We may disclose Information in order to comply with the law, regulation, a judicial proceeding, subpoena, court order, or other legal process. 

We may disclose to our Advertisers and other third parties aggregated or de-identified information about users for marketing, advertising, research, or other purposes. 

### 5\. Retention period

The Advertisers and Affiliates personal data collected for contractual reasons shall be detained for an undetermined period as long as the contractual relationship lasts. Once the contractual relation finishes, the information shall be stored for a period of six years according to the law. 

### 6\. Data Transfers

We store the Personal Data that we hold about You in the European Union (“EU”). Given the fact that we are an international company, we also transfer your Personal Data to non-European countries where data protection laws may be less protective than the legislation where you live. 

When such a transfer happens, we ensure that We get your consent and that it takes place in accordance with this Privacy Notice and is regulated by standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission as ensuring an adequate protection for data subjects. 

### 7\. Web Browser Cookies

We might use cookies and other similar technologies, such as web beacons, pixels, and mobile identifiers to understand the website usage and to improve the functioning of the service, in order to ensure a more efficient and seamless navigation. We may also allow our business partners to use these tracking technologies on our website or engage others to track your behavior on our behalf. 

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to help us analyze how You use our site. A cookie is a small data file able to track the online movements of an individual on a specific website. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. 

We may additionally collect information using Web beacons, which are commonly referred to in the industry as web bugs, pixel tags or Clear GIFs. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on the Site or in our emails to deliver cookies, count visits and determine if an email has been opened and acted upon. 

### 8\. Rights of the Data Subjects

While We process your personal data you have a series of rights so that you can decide and control at all times how We use your Personal Data. You can exercise these rights at any time and for free. To exercise your rights, you simply have to send us an email to . In order to meet your request, we need to make sure that it is really you, so you must provide us with a copy of your identity document; we would also appreciate if you could indicate the right you wish to exercise. If your request does not meet the above requirements, we will ask you to complete it. 

##### 8.1. Right to be informed of the lawful basis for processing

The right to be informed of the purpose for which  process the personal data and the lawful basis for the processing, which is the legitimate interest of the company. 

##### 8.2. Right to be informed of transfers to third parties

The right to be informed that the personal data collected may be transferred to the following third parties: 

  * Banks
  * Tax Administration
  * Administrative Management of Customers and Suppliers
  * Judicial Organs
  * Local Police
  * Other Bodies of the State Administration
  * Other bodies of the Autonomous Community
  * Provincial Councils
  * Other organs of the Local Adm.
  * Notaries lawyers and solicitors

##### 8.3. Right to withdraw content at any time – Opting-Out

If You supply us with your e-mail address, you may receive periodic e-mails from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know. However, we may still contact you concerning administrative or transactional matters. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know. 

##### 8.4. Right to have their personal data secured

Your personal data shall be stored in a secure and confidential way.

##### 8.5. Right to Erasure

You are able to request your personal data We store to be erased at any moment. Whenever this is requested, the company might be unable in some circumstances to comply with legal obligations and the User will be informed about the implications of that decision. 

##### 8.6. Right of access

You may request access to your personal data We store. The data shall be provided in a portable format easily accessible by the User. 

##### 8.7. Right to Rectification

You may request to correct any information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect or misleading. 

##### 8.8. Right to lodge a complaint

You have the right to file a complaint before the competent supervisory authority, at any moment, if deemed appropriate. 

### 9\. Children under 18

Our Site and products or services available through the Site are not intended for children under 18 years old. We do not knowingly solicit data online from or market online to children under 18 years-old. If we knowingly receive a child’s personally identifiable information, we will immediately delete it from our system. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 18 years old and you believe we have received personal information from your child, please contact us at . 

### 10\. Data security

We adopt reasonable data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

Data access is limited to our authorized employees as part of their work or to potential service providers as part of the performance of a service. Potential contractors that we might hired are subject to the same obligations. 

You should note that the security of your personal information also depends on you. Please do not communicate any information to us through unsecured channels, such as when you are in public areas. Where we have provided you or you have chosen a password, access code, or similar security feature, you must keep the password, access code or security feature confidential. Please do not share your password with anyone. If you believe your password or account has been compromised, please contact us immediately at . 

Please note that the transmission of information via the Internet or other means of communication is not completely secure. Although we take reasonable measure to secure your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Site or through other means of communication. Any transmission of information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy setting or security measures contained on any of our systems, including but not limited to our Site. 

Updated on the 16th of July 2018.
